Yumi
유미
Yumi's Cells
유미의 세포
Episode 09 Frog
09화 개구리
The lights came on!
불이 켜졌다!
- Sensitivity, are you all right? - I'm all right.
- 예민아, 괜찮아? - 난 괜찮아요.
What is this?
이게 뭔가요?
Isn't this snow?
이거 눈 아니야?
- What is this? - Why is it suddenly snowing?
- 이게 뭔가요? - 왜 갑자기 눈이 오나요?
Wow, it is sweet.
와, 달콤해요.
It is sweet!
달콤해요!
- It's sweet! - I'm mad!
- 달콤해요! - 나 화났어!
Is it sugar snow? How is this happening?
설탕눈인가? 어떻게 이런 일이 일어나고 있나요?
Yumi didn't eat anything, though.
그런데 유미는 아무것도 먹지 않았어요.
That's not it, Reason.
그게 아니야, 이유.
Then?
그 다음에?
Why are you standing in the rain?
왜 비를 맞으며 서 있나요?
You'll catch a cold like that.
그런 식으로 감기에 걸리게 됩니다.
There are so many other sweet things in the world besides sugar.
세상에는 설탕 말고도 달콤한 것들이 너무 많아요.
Excuse me, hello.
실례합니다. 안녕하세요.
Excuse me, Oppa Wung.
실례합니다, 웅오빠.
Hello, I'm Ruby.
안녕하세요, 저는 루비입니다.
Oh, yes.
아, 그렇죠.
Did you come to see Eonni? I was really surprised.
언니 보러 오셨나요? 정말 놀랐어요.
- Let's talk later. - Ah, all right.
- 나중에 얘기하자. - 아, 알았어.
- Where are you going? - Home.
- 어디 가세요? - 집.
Let's go. I will take you home.
갑시다. 내가 집에 데려다줄게.
There's something different about him from the last time I saw him. Why does he look so neat?
그 사람은 지난번에 봤을 때와 뭔가 달라진 게 있어요. 그 사람은 왜 이렇게 깔끔해 보이는 걸까요?
Taxi!
택시!
Because of the rain, there seems to be no available taxi. I can't even request one.
비 때문에 이용할 수 있는 택시가 없는 것 같습니다. 나는 하나도 요청할 수 없습니다.
But...
하지만...
Why did you come here? - Huh?
왜 여기에 왔나요? - 뭐?
Why did you come here at so late in the day?
왜 이렇게 늦은 시간에 여기에 왔나요?
Oh ...
아...
I had something to do nearby.
근처에 할 일이 있었어요.
Something to do?
할 일이 있나요?
Well ...
음...
To be honest ... I was curious,
솔직히... 궁금했는데,
since you didn't reply.
당신이 대답하지 않았기 때문에.
I was curious why you didn't reply.
왜 답장을 안 했는지 궁금했어요.
My phone was broken, so it is at the repair shop.
휴대폰이 고장 나서 수리점에 있어요.
Really?
정말?
Ah, so that's what happened!
아, 그래서 그런 일이 일어났구나!
I thought...
내 생각엔...
I got rejected.
나는 거절당했습니다.
It has been a while since sugar snow came down like this. right?
이렇게 설탕눈이 내린 건 오랜만이다. 오른쪽?
True, I think it's been years since I last saw it.
사실, 마지막으로 본 지 몇 년은 된 것 같아요.
That's right.
좋아요.
Who are you?
누구세요?
Gatekeeper cells, hello! I came from Wung's village.
게이트키퍼 셀들, 안녕하세요! 나는 웅의 마을에서 왔습니다.
Wung's cell? But why did you show up here?
웅의 세포요? 그런데 왜 여기에 나타났어요?
I want to visit Yumi's village. What is the password?
유미네 마을을 방문하고 싶어요. 비밀번호는 무엇입니까?
What?! Do you think a man can easily get into Yumi's heart? Do you?!
무엇?! 남자가 유미의 마음에 쉽게 들어갈 수 있을 것 같나요? 당신은?!
This door has a password that is twenty-eight digits.
이 문에는 28자리의 비밀번호가 있습니다.
Twenty eight? Why is it so long? Wung's village password is only four digits.
스물여덟? 왜 이렇게 길어? 웅의 마을 비밀번호는 네 자리뿐이다.
If you know now, leave. For the past three years, nobody has been able to get through this door.
이제 알았으면 떠나세요. 지난 3년 동안 누구도 이 문을 통과하지 못했습니다.
- Yumi is not an easy woman. - That's right.
- 유미는 쉬운 여자가 아니다. - 좋아요.
Can you just let me in? The mood is great right now.
그냥 들여보내 주실 수 있나요? 지금은 기분이 좋습니다.
- Get out! - Why, I ought to...!
- 나가세요! - 왜, 그래야만 하는데...!
Searching for an available taxi.
이용 가능한 택시를 검색 중입니다.
Miss Yumi, the requests keep getting canceled. Should we go somewhere nearby--
유미씨, 요청이 계속 취소되고 있어요. 근처 어딘가로 갈까--
Miss Yumi?
유미씨?
It isn't rain. It is sweat.
비가 아닙니다. 땀입니다.
Her temperature seems to be around 38 degrees Celsius.
체온은 38도 정도 되는 것 같습니다.
It is an emergency! It is an emergency! Everyone focus
긴급 상황입니다! 긴급 상황입니다! 다들 집중해
The goal from now on is to make sure we take Yumi to the hospital safely!
이제부터 목표는 유미를 병원까지 안전하게 데려가는 것!
We don't have much time! Run the algorithm!
시간이 별로 없어요! 알고리즘을 실행해보세요!
Loading
로드 중
We will start running Wung's algorithm.
Wung의 알고리즘을 실행해 보겠습니다.
Start
시작
Is there a hospital nearby?
근처에 병원이 있나요?
Yes or No
예 또는 아니요
Miss Yumi, wait a sec.
유미 씨, 잠깐만요.
Is there a hospital nearby? Yes or No.
근처에 병원이 있나요? 예 또는 아니요.
Is there a hospital nearby?
근처에 병원이 있나요?
YES
예
Is it a distance where you can run and carry her there?
그녀를 데리고 달려갈 수 있는 거리인가요?
Are you in a relationship where you can carry this princess?
당신은 이 공주님을 안고 다닐 수 있는 연애를 하고 있나요?
NO
아니요
Is this the time to nitpick over that?
지금이 그것에 대해 질의할 시간인가요?
It isn't.
그렇지 않습니다.
Use skills to carry the princess.
스킬을 사용하여 공주를 운반하세요.
Complete 100%
100% 완료
Can you carry the umbrella?
우산을 가지고 다닐 수 있나요?
NO
아니요
Forget about it
잊어버려
Starting now, all the carbohydrates stored in the body will be released.
이제부터 몸에 저장된 탄수화물이 모두 배출됩니다.
Wung Sprint Mode. Start.
웅 스프린트 모드. 시작.
Start Sprint mode ♫ There is a me I don't know.. ♫
시작 스프린트 모드 ♫ 내가 모르는 내가 있다.. ♫
♫ Even if I walk slowly ♫
♫ 천천히 걸어도 ♫
♫ my heart is there far away. ♫
♫ 내 마음은 저 멀리 거기에 있어요. ♫
♫ I wouldn't know why it's like that ♫
♫ 왜 그런 것인지 모르겠어요 ♫
♫ Even f I walk carefully ♫
♫ 조심스럽게 걸어도 ♫
♫ my heart is there far away ♫
♫ 내 마음은 저 멀리 거기 있어요 ♫
♫ It's racing wide awake ♫
♫ 잠에서 깨어나 질주하고 있어요 ♫
Excuse me! Wait! Over here, over here!
실례합니다! 기다리다! 여기, 여기!
Wait! Please take a look at her she's an emergency patient!
기다리다! 그녀를 좀 봐주세요 그녀는 응급 환자입니다!
She's an emergency patient. Hurry!
응급환자입니다. 서두르다!
♫ Even if I spend a day when nothing happens ♫
♫ 아무 일도 일어나지 않는 하루를 보내도 ♫
♫ My heart is heading somewhere ♫
♫ 내 마음은 어딘가로 향하고 있어요 ♫
♫ Even I still don't know ♫
♫ 나도 아직은 모르겠어 ♫
♫ It's running there far away ♫
♫ 저 멀리 저쪽으로 달려가고 있어요 ♫
♫ It shouldn't be running so fast ♫
♫ 너무 빨리 돌아가면 안 돼요 ♫
Guardian.
보호자.
You are the guardian, right?
당신이 보호자죠?
Are you Kim Yumi's guardian? NO
김유미의 보호자이신가요? 아니요
Although you are not the guardian, do you want to be her guardian?
당신은 보호자는 아니지만 그녀의 보호자가 되고 싶나요?
YES
예
Yes, I am the guardian.
네, 제가 보호자입니다.
Her fever went down, so she just needs to get some IV fluids.
열이 떨어졌기 때문에 IV 수액만 투여하면 됩니다.
All right, thank you.
알겠습니다. 감사합니다.
But since the patient's clothes are all wet, I think it would be good to prepare a change of clothes.
그런데 환자 옷이 다 젖었으니 갈아입을 옷을 준비하는 게 좋을 것 같아요.
It takes about an hour to get all the IV fluids.
IV 수액을 모두 받는 데 약 1시간이 걸립니다.
All right, thank you.
알겠습니다. 감사합니다.
The situation is over. Mission clear.
상황은 끝났습니다. 미션 클리어.
Starting now begins self-admiring mode.
지금 시작하면 자기 감탄 모드가 시작됩니다.
Self-admiring mode
자기 감탄 모드
- Hello? - Where are you? [Self-admiring]
- 안녕하세요? - 어디세요? [자기 감탄]
Why aren't you coming? We're eating pajeon*. Where are you? (Savoury Korean pancake with green onions)
왜 안 와요? 우리는 파전을 먹습니다*. 어디세요? (파를 넣은 맛있는 한국식 전)
- The hospital?
- 병원요?
Why are you at the hospital?
왜 병원에 있나요?
Miss Yumi? Why?
유미씨? 왜?
You punk, I wondered where you went. You went to her office?
이 새끼야, 네가 어디로 갔는지 궁금했어. 그 사람 사무실에 갔었어?
If I hadn't gone, it could have been a disaster.
내가 가지 않았다면 재앙이 되었을 수도 있다.
She had a high fever and she fainted.
그녀는 고열이 나서 의식을 잃었습니다.
How were you able to take an unconscious person to the hospital?
의식을 잃은 사람을 어떻게 병원에 데려갈 수 있었나요?
I carried her and ran. Of course, it definitely wasn't easy. [Self-admiring]
나는 그녀를 안고 달렸다. 물론 확실히 쉽지는 않았습니다. [자기 감탄]
I ran while holding her for about ten minutes.
나는 그녀를 안고 10분 정도 달렸다.
You ran carrying her for ten minutes? You really have strong arms.
그녀를 안고 10분 동안 뛰었나요? 당신은 정말 강한 팔을 갖고 있어요.
They're still numb.
그들은 여전히 ​​​​무감각합니다.
Miss Yumi is light. She's light as a feather. I wonder why my arms are numb.
유미 씨는 가볍습니다. 그녀는 깃털처럼 가볍습니다. 팔이 왜 저리는지 궁금합니다.
- Give it to me. - You just wait! Hold on.
- 나한테 줘. - 기다리세요! 기다리다.
Say something.
말해보세요.
Hello. You went after a woman who didn't reply to your message?
안녕하세요. You went after a woman who didn't reply to your message?
No, it turned out she broke her phone and left it to be repaired.
아니요, 알고 보니 그녀는 휴대폰을 망가뜨려 수리를 맡기고 떠났습니다.
What is she supposed to say to someone who came to find her? It was an excuse.
그녀를 찾으러 온 사람에게 그녀는 뭐라고 말해야 할까요? 그것은 변명이었습니다.
An excuse?
변명?
You idiot.
바보야.
- Well, so what? She's ill. - You're hopeless.
- 그럼 어쩌죠? 그녀는 아프다. - 당신은 절망적이에요.
- I just followed my algorithm. - What?
- 난 그냥 내 알고리즘을 따랐어요. - 무엇?
According to my algorithm, this was the right choice.
내 알고리즘에 따르면 이것이 올바른 선택이었습니다.
You two have dinner on your own. I'm going to take miss Yumi home when she wakes up.
둘이서 저녁을 먹습니다. 유미씨가 깨어나면 제가 집에 데려갈 예정이에요.
See you tomorrow.
내일 봐요.
Does he not have a brain? Why would he go there?
그 사람은 뇌가 없나요? 그는 왜 거기로 갈까요?
He's completely smitten with her.
그는 그녀에게 완전히 반했습니다.
He's just completely smitten with Kim Yumi.
그는 김유미에게 완전히 반했습니다.
It would look good on her.
그녀에게 좋을 것 같아요.
Are you awake?
깨어있나요?
Your boyfriend left this for you.
당신의 남자친구가 당신을 위해 이것을 남겼습니다.
My boyfriend?
내 남자친구요?
Your boyfriend went through a lot of trouble, getting soaked in the rain.
당신의 남자 친구는 비에 젖어 많은 어려움을 겪었습니다.
I was afraid he might catch a cold, but he went out to buy some clothes.
감기에 걸릴까 봐 걱정됐지만 옷을 사러 나갔다.
Your old clothes got all wet, so you should change into this.
낡은 옷이 다 젖었으니 이것으로 갈아입으세요.
- Stay put for a moment. - All right.
- 잠시만 가만히 계세요. - 괜찮은.
It's a dress.
드레스예요.
It's cute.
귀엽네요.
Should we have just let in Wung's cell?
그냥 Wung의 감방을 들여보내야 했던 걸까요?
But the password is so long.
그런데 비밀번호가 너무 길어요.
True, true. Yumi's heart isn't easy to reach.
사실, 사실입니다. 유미의 마음은 쉽게 닿지 않는다.
- It's not easy. It's not easy. - Of course not.
- 쉽지 않아요. 쉽지 않습니다. - 당연하지.
Hey! Who are you?!
여기요! 누구세요?!
It's a frog. What should we do?
개구리입니다. 우리는 무엇을 해야 합니까?
Should we let it in? Cute things can enter without a password.
들여보내야 할까요? 귀여운 것들은 비밀번호 없이 들어갈 수 있어요.
That is true, but ... hold on.
그건 사실이지만... 잠깐만요.
The things that Yumi thinks are cute are puppies,
유미가 귀엽다고 생각하는 것들은 강아지들,
cats, chicks,
고양이, 병아리,
panda bears, and ... Oh! Frogs aren't on the list.
팬더곰, 그리고... 오! 개구리는 목록에 없습니다.
So what? Let's just open the doors, it looks cute anyway.
그래서 뭐? 그냥 문을 열자, 어쨌든 귀여워 보인다.
- Should we? - Ribbit.
- 그래야 할까요? - 개빗.
All right, why not.
좋아요, 왜 안되죠?
On a rainy day, a frog
비오는 날 개구리
made its way into Yumi's heart.
유미의 마음에 들어왔습니다.
- Who are you? - Ribbit.
- 누구세요? - 개빗.
The frog that entered Yumi's heart like that, saved us cells.
그렇게 유미의 마음 속으로 들어온 개구리가 우리의 세포를 구해줬어요.
It successfully sutured Hunger's taste buds back on.
Hunger의 미뢰를 성공적으로 봉합했습니다.
He cleaned the village that had become polluted from stress,
스트레스로 오염된 마을을 청소했고,
and built a fence so Hysterius couldn't come back.
그리고 히스테리우스가 돌아오지 못하도록 울타리를 쳤습니다.
Love, look! Someone's coming!
사랑해요, 보세요! 누군가 오고 있어요!
He even found Love and Inner Feelings who had been stranded on a deserted island.
그는 무인도에 고립된 사랑과 내면의 감정도 발견했다.
The frog did all of this by himself.
개구리는 이 모든 일을 혼자서 해냈습니다.
Although we just met, thank you so much, Frog.
만난 지 얼마 안 됐는데 정말 고마워요, 개구리님.
- Love, I'm actually not a frog. - What?
- 얘야, 난 사실 개구리가 아니야. - 무엇?
I played a small trick so I could enter Yumi's heart.
나는 유미의 마음에 들어갈 수 있도록 작은 속임수를 썼다.
The password to Yumi's heart is too hard, you see.
유미 마음의 비밀번호가 너무 어렵네요.
Then, who are you?
그렇다면 당신은 누구입니까?
Hi, Yumi's Love cell.
안녕하세요 유미의 러브셀입니다.
- Who are you? - I am Wung's love cell!
- 누구세요? - 나는 웅의 사랑세포다!
- What?
- 무엇?
- It's cute. - Wung's love cell disguised himself as a frog
- 귀엽네요. - 개구리로 변장한 웅의 사랑세포
and entered Yumi's heart.
그리고 유미의 마음 속으로 들어갔습니다.
Oh! You're up.
오! 당신은 일어났습니다.
How are you feeling?
기분이 어때요?
Even Yumi didn't know
유미도 몰랐어요
when he came into her heart.
그가 그녀의 마음에 들어왔을 때.
Are you still feeling unwell?
아직도 몸이 안 좋으세요?
No. I'm fine.
아뇨. 저는 괜찮아요.
But ... where did you buy this?
그런데... 이거 어디서 샀어요?
Somewhere nearby. I chose it as best as I could because I didn't know your size.
근처 어딘가에. 고객님의 사이즈를 모르기 때문에 최선을 다해 선택했습니다.
You don't like it?
당신은 그것을 좋아하지 않습니까?
I do like it.
나는 그것을 정말로 좋아한다.
You do?
당신은요?
Yes. I like it.
예. 좋아요.
It reminded me of the frog festival.
개구리 축제가 생각나더군요.
Exactly, it's cute.
바로, 귀엽습니다.
You wearing that is cuter.
그걸 입으신게 더 귀엽네요.
You're really good at flattery.
당신은 아첨을 정말 잘해요.
It's not flattery. I told you I can't lie.
그것은 아첨이 아닙니다. 나는 거짓말을 할 수 없다고 말했습니다.
I'll go pay the bill.
내가 가서 요금을 지불할게.
Do you want to have dinner with me?
나랑 저녁 먹을래?
You didn't eat yet, right?
아직 식사 안 하신 거죠?
Let me repay you. I'll buy you something good.
보답하겠습니다. 내가 좋은 거 사줄게.
Repay?
갚다?
Yes, because I'm grateful.
네, 감사하기 때문이죠.
There's nothing to be grateful for. Anyone would've done what I did—
감사할 것이 하나도 없습니다. 누구라도 내가 한 일을 했을 것입니다—
To tell the truth, I'm trying to ask you out on a second date.
사실대로 말하자면, 당신에게 두 번째 데이트를 신청하려고 합니다.
Eat dinner with me.
나랑 저녁 먹어요.
Oh.
오.
Are you rejecting a second date?
두 번째 데이트를 거부하시나요?
No, not at all. It's just that it's so late, so I think most places are closed.
아니요, 전혀 그렇지 않습니다. 단지 시간이 너무 늦어서 대부분의 장소가 문을 닫은 것 같아요.
They'll still be open until 9 pm.
그들은 여전히 ​​오후 9시까지 열려 있을 거예요.
9 pm? What time is it now?
오후 9시? 지금은 몇시입니까?
What time is it? It's Seoul*. (*T/N: Seoul the city sounds the same as Seoul time.)
지금은 몇시입니까? 서울*입니다. (*T/N: 서울의 시간은 서울의 시간과 동일하게 들립니다.)
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
I'm a gentleman*.
나는 신사*입니다.
*(This sounds the same as "I am Sim Sa Im Dang," a Korean artist from the Joseon Dynasty. She is on Korea's 50,000
*(조선시대 화가 '심사임당입니다'와 같은 소리네요. 한국 5만명에 해당하는 분
That was good.
좋았어요.
Episode 10 Bulletin Board
10회 게시판
When Yumi is asleep, in the middle of the night,
유미가 자고 있을 때 한밤중에
the Dream Theater starts its late-night screening.
드림시어터가 심야상영을 시작합니다.
Wow, what's going to happen today?
와, 오늘 무슨 일이 일어날까요?
It reminded me of the frog festival.
개구리 축제가 생각나더군요.
Exactly, it's cute.
바로, 귀엽습니다.
You wearing that is cuter.
그걸 입으신게 더 귀엽네요.
Must be nice.
분명 좋을 거야.
Today's screening is a romantic comedy production.
오늘 상영회는 로맨틱 코미디 작품입니다.
It's over there.
저기 있어요.
- That house? - Yes, I live on the fourth floor there.
- 그 집? - 네, 저는 그곳 4층에 살아요.
Thank you for today and also for taking me home.
오늘 하루도 고맙고 집에 데려다줘서 고마워요.
- Get some rest and make sure to take your medicine. - All right.
- 휴식을 취하고 약을 꼭 복용하세요. - 알았어.
I'll go now.
나는 지금 갈 것이다.
Text me when you get home.
집에 오면 문자 주세요.
Text you?
문자를 보내시겠어요?
Because it is very late now.
지금은 너무 늦었으니까요.
But it will take more than thirty minutes.
하지만 30분 이상 걸릴 거예요.
It's all right.
괜찮아요.
But you don't have your cellphone.
그런데 당신은 휴대폰이 없어요.
Oh, right.
아, 그렇죠.
Good night.
안녕히 주무세요.
I have my laptop. I can use Messenger on it.
나는 노트북을 가지고 있습니다. 메신저를 사용할 수 있어요.
- Are you serious? - Yes.
- 진심이에요? - 네.
Is it all right for me to wake you up?
내가 당신을 깨워도 괜찮을까요?
I'm telling you that it's fine.
괜찮다고 말해주고 있어요.
I'm not perceptive, so if you tell me to do it I really will do it.
저는 눈치가 없어서 하라고 하면 정말 할게요.
Please do.
그렇게 해주세요.
Go inside now.
지금 안으로 들어가세요.
To be continued
계속됩니다
Dream Theatre
드림 시어터
Wow! Every scene was good today.
와! 오늘은 모든 장면이 좋았다.
After the late-night screening is over and all the cells are asleep,
심야 심사가 끝나고 모든 세포가 잠든 후
there is a cell that starts working only then.
그때에만 작동을 시작하는 셀이 있습니다.
When the cells post their thoughts on the bulletin board throughout the day,
세포들이 하루종일 자신의 생각을 게시판에 올리면
- Ruby is so annoying! - Wound Documenter - There's a lot of expenses lately. - Stingy
- 루비는 정말 짜증나! - 상처 기록기 - 요즘 지출이 너무 많아요. - 인색함
We need more masks. - Anxiety cell
마스크가 더 필요합니다. - 불안세포
Those thoughts have an impact on Yumi's life the next day.
그 생각은 다음날 유미의 삶에 영향을 미쳤다.
What exactly is love? - Sensitivity cell
사랑이란 정확히 무엇입니까? - 민감도 셀
The Bulletin Board cell throws away the useless stories.
게시판 셀은 쓸데없는 이야기를 버립니다.
The dongaseu* restaurant we ate at today was the best! - Hunger *(Pork cutlet)
오늘 우리가 먹은 동가스* 식당이 최고였어요! - 배고픔 *(돈까스)
Wung lives in Jeongbalsan. - Reason
웅은 정발산에 산다. - 이유
And he moves the stories that she has to remember to the top of the bulletin board.
그리고 그녀가 기억해야 할 이야기들을 게시판 상단으로 옮긴다.
Huh? What is this?
응? 이것은 무엇입니까?
Sometimes he finds old thoughts that he doesn't even know when they were written.
때때로 그는 언제 쓰여졌는지조차 모르는 오래된 생각을 발견합니다.
Since when has this been here?
언제부터 여기 있었지?
This is anonymous too. If these are left on here, Yumi gets stressed.
이것도 익명입니다. 여기에 놔두면 유미가 스트레스를 받거든요.
Chae Wu Gi is your destiny?
채우기가 당신의 운명인가요?
Destiny does not exist. It's all a choice.
운명은 존재하지 않습니다. 그것은 모두 선택입니다.
♫ Sing a song song song song song ♫
♫ 노래 노래 노래 노래 노래 ♫
♫ so that I can feel your love love love love ♫
♫ 너의 사랑을 느낄 수 있게 사랑 사랑 사랑 ♫
♫ Can't think the word that I wanna say ♫
♫ 내가 말하고 싶은 단어가 생각나지 않네요 ♫
I'm almost home now.
이제 집에 거의 다 왔어요.
You got home home late.
집에 늦게 오셨어요.
It's because I couldn't get a taxi. Didn't you fall asleep yet?
택시를 탈 수 없었기 때문이다. 아직 잠들지 않았나요?
I'm going to sleep now.
나는 지금 자러 갈거야.
Goodnight.
안녕히 주무세요.
♫ I wish someone lives there ♫
♫ 누군가 거기에 살았으면 좋겠어요 ♫
♫ For so many questions ♫
♫ 질문이 너무 많아서 ♫
Can I...
내가...
Yes?
응?
Can I call you tomorrow?
내일 전화해도 될까요?
Yes.
그렇습니다.
Goodnight for real.
정말 잘 자요.
♫ I thought I would be a fabulous adult ♫
♫ 나는 멋진 어른이 될 거라고 생각했어요 ♫
♫ You don't know how I feel ♫
♫ 당신은 내 기분이 어떤지 모르실 거예요 ♫
♫ My hair and makeup are pathetic ♫
♫ 머리랑 화장이 한심해 ♫
♫ It's not about something I can understand ♫
♫ 내가 이해할 수 있는 문제는 아니야 ♫
Sorry, put this up too.
죄송해요, 이것도 올려주세요.
♫ Sing a song song song song song ♫
♫ 노래 노래 노래 노래 노래 ♫
Oh! This is a good comment.
오! 좋은 댓글이네요.
Good job!
잘했어요!
♫ so that I can feel your love love love love ♫
♫ 너의 사랑 사랑 사랑 사랑 느낄 수 있게 ♫
Go on a date tomorrow too. - Love
내일도 데이트하세요. - 사랑
Everyone has their own bulletin board. Of course, Wung does too.
누구에게나 자신만의 게시판이 있습니다. 물론 Wung도 그렇습니다.
Yumi is cute.
유미는 귀엽습니다.
Yumi likes dongaseu.
유미는 돈가스를 좋아해요.
Kim Yumi looks cute in short hair.
김유미는 짧은 머리도 귀여운 것 같아요.
The hoodie dress looks good on Yumi.
후드티 드레스가 유미에게 잘 어울리네요.
Yumi's house is on the fourth floor.
유미의 집은 4층에 있어요.
Oh yay! Go on a date tomorrow too!
아 예! 내일도 데이트하세요!
Stop posting about Yumi! Go to sleep!
유미 관련 포스팅은 이제 그만! 자러 가세요!
♫ I wish someone lives there ♫
♫ 누군가 거기에 살았으면 좋겠어요 ♫
♫ For so many questions ♫
♫ 질문이 너무 많아서 ♫
I'm back.
나는 돌아왔다.
Where did they go?
그들은 어디로 갔나요?
She's cute, Kim Yumi.
귀여워 김유미.
She is Gu Wung's type.
그녀는 Gu Wung 유형입니다.
Hello. Did you just get home?
안녕하세요. 방금 집에 왔나요?
Where are you? Why aren't you here? Only your bags are there.
어디세요? 왜 여기 없나요? 거기엔 당신 가방만 있어요.
We're still at that pajeon restaurant.
우리는 아직 그 파전 식당에 있어요.
You guys are still eating?
너희들 아직도 먹고 있어?
What happened?
무슨 일이에요?
- What? - You said Miss Yumi was sick.
- 무엇? - 유미 씨가 아프다고 했잖아요.
- Is she all right? - Yes, she got better.
- 그 사람 괜찮아요? - 응, 좋아졌어.
That's good. And?
좋아요. 그리고?
And, what?
그리고 뭐?
And, did you ask her to meet you again?
그리고, 그 사람한테 다시 만나자고 했었나요?
Yes. It wasn't an excuse that her cellphone was broken.
예. 휴대폰이 고장난 것은 변명이 아니었다.
She probably felt sorry and agreed to go on a second date.
그녀는 아마도 안타까움을 느끼고 두 번째 데이트를 하기로 동의했을 것입니다.
No, she was the one to ask me to go on a second date.
아니, 나한테 두 번째 데이트를 하자고 한 사람이 그 사람이었어.
- No way. - I'm serious.
- 안 돼요. - 진심이에요.
Oh! Gu Wung is finally dating?
오! 구웅 드디어 사귄다?
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
- 축하해요. - 감사합니다.
I was going to call you anyway. Come and take Louis back home.
어차피 너한테 전화하려고 했어. 와서 루이스를 집으로 데려가세요.
- Why? - He's totally knocked out.
- 왜? - 완전히 기절했어요.
Wake him up.
그를 깨워라.
He won't wake up, no matter what I do.
내가 무엇을 하든 그 사람은 깨어나지 않을 거예요.
All right.
괜찮은.
Welcome.
환영.
You're here?
당신은 여기에 있습니까?
Did you drink a lot?
많이 마셨나요?
A little?
조금?
- Why? - Since you got a girlfriend.
- 왜? - 여자친구 생겼으니까.
Louis, let's go. Get up
루이스, 가자. 일어나
Sit down.
앉으세요.
We should go. It is past midnight.
우리는 가야 해요. 자정이 지났습니다.
There is still some of this left. It would be a waste. Let's go after we finish it.
아직 이게 좀 남아있습니다. 그것은 낭비일 것이다. 다 마친 후에 가자.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Ma'am, please give us another pajeon.
부인, 파전 하나 더 주세요.
All right.
괜찮은.
- We are going to leave soon, though. - You like the pajeon from here.
- 하지만 우리는 곧 떠날 예정이에요. - 여기 파전이 맘에 드네요.
I'm buying, so don't worry and drink.
내가 사니까 걱정하지 말고 마셔.
Are you happy now that you're dating?
이제 연애하는 게 행복해요?
I've only met her twice until now.
나는 지금까지 그녀를 딱 두 번 만났습니다.
That's why it is good. What a thrilling second meeting.
그렇기 때문에 좋은 것입니다. 정말 스릴 넘치는 두 번째 만남이었습니다.
It was worth shaving off the beard you'd been growing for three years.
3년 동안 길러온 수염을 깎을 만한 가치가 있었습니다.
- I suddenly thought of that. - What?
- 문득 그런 생각이 들었어요. - 무엇?
Sitting here with Louis is sleeping and while were drinking dongdongju*, (Traditional rice liquor)
여기 루이와 함께 앉아 자고 동동주를 마시며, (전통 쌀주)
doesn't make you think of the past?
과거가 생각나지 않나요?
That dongdongju place in Hapjeong-dong.
합정동에 있는 동동주라는 곳이에요.
You remember the dongdongju place
동동주 장소를 기억하시나요
where we used to go to often, right?
우리 자주 가던 곳 맞죠?
Danger detected! Danger detected!
위험이 감지되었습니다! 위험이 감지되었습니다!
Danger sensed! Sae Yi is trying to talk about the past.
Danger sensed! 세이는 과거에 대해 이야기하려고 한다.
- No, when Sae Yi drinks and talks about the past, there's always a hidden motive. - That's right!
- 아니, 세이가 술을 마시며 과거를 이야기할 때는 항상 숨은 동기가 숨어 있다. - 좋아요!
It is dangerous. From now on Wung will be in defense mode.
위험합니다. 이제부터 Wung은 방어 모드에 들어갑니다.
Understood.
이해했다.
Wung is switching to defense mode.
Wung이 방어 모드로 전환하고 있습니다.
Changing to bear mode.
곰 모드로 변경됩니다.
Starting now, Wung will be a bear.
이제부터 Wung은 곰이 됩니다.
Someone who doesn't understand what you're saying and has no perception.
당신이 말하는 것을 이해하지 못하고 인식이 없는 사람.
He will be dull and won't be able to remember the past.
그는 둔해지고 과거를 기억하지 못할 것입니다.
Okay, this is good!
좋아, 이거 좋다!
Back at that dongdongju place, when I was really drunk,
그 동동주에서 엄청 취했을 때,
there was a time you came to pick me up. You remember, right?
당신이 나를 데리러 올 때가 있었어요. 기억나지?
- I did? - You know, the day it was snowing a lot!
- 내가 그랬어? - 눈이 많이 내리던 날!
It snowed?
눈이 왔나요?
You came to pick me up and saw that I was drunk, so you got really angry.
당신은 나를 데리러 왔다가 내가 취한 것을 보고 몹시 화를 냈습니다.
Why were you so angry back then?
그땐 왜 그렇게 화가 났어요?
When?
언제?
When you were working at a company.
회사에 다니던 시절.
- Company? - When you were living in Hapjeong-dong, there was a dongdongju place nearby. You don't remember?
- 회사? - 합정동에 살 때 근처에 동동주라는 곳이 있었어요. 기억하지 못하시나요?
Dongdongju place in Hapjeong-dong?
합정동에 동동주가 있나요?
Where is that?
그게 어디야?
Nevermind. Forget about it.
괜찮아요. 잊어버리세요.
Defense successful.
방어에 성공했습니다.
You used to like me, right?
당신은 나를 좋아했었죠?
That's right!
좋아요!
The cold wind keeps coming in. Is it all right there?
찬바람이 계속 들어오네요. 거기 괜찮나요?
The second attack is about to start.
두 번째 공격이 곧 시작됩니다.
Sae Yi's ulterior motive: I want to sit next to you.
새이의 숨은 동기: 옆에 앉고 싶다.
Should I move over there? It is cold.
저쪽으로 이사가야 하나? 춥습니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
You should have told me sooner.
좀 더 일찍 말했어야 했는데.
I was really hot, this works out.
나는 정말 더웠어요.
- I wasn't asking you to change seats... - Huh?
- 자리 바꿔달라고 한 건 아니었는데... - 응?
Nevermind.
괜찮아요.
Defense successful.
방어에 성공했습니다.
- Please enjoy. - Thank you.
- 즐겨주세요. - 감사합니다.
It looks good.
좋아 보인다.
Aren't you going to eat?
식사 안 가시나요?
I'm full.
배불러요
This is a lot.
이것은 많은 것입니다.
Wung...
웅...
The third attack is about to start.
세 번째 공격이 곧 시작됩니다.
Sae Yi's ulterior motive: Saying the truth while drunk
새이의 숨은 동기: 술에 취해 진실을 말하는 것
Should I tell you a secret?
비밀 하나 말해줄까?
- No. - Why not?
- 아니. - 왜 안돼?
It is a secret, so why would you tell? You don't have to tell me.
비밀인데 왜 말하겠어요? 나에게 말할 필요는 없습니다.
You know that I had a crush on someone when I was in college, right?
제가 대학시절 누군가를 짝사랑했던거 아시죠?
Do you know who that guy was?
그 사람이 누군지 아세요?
- Seonbae Jin Su? - What?
- 선배 진수요? - 무엇?
- Seonbae Jin Su. - No, I really didn't like him.
- 선배 진수. - 아니, 난 그 사람을 정말 좋아하지 않았어.
- It is right! It was Seonbae Jin Su. - I told you it wasn't!
- 맞아요! 선배진수였습니다. - 아니라고 했잖아!
I had such a hard time because there were rumors that I liked him.
좋아한다는 소문이 있어서 너무 힘들었어요.
Everyone knows that it was Seonbae Jin Su.
선배 진수였다는 건 다들 아시죠?
It isn't! Who started that rumor?
그렇지 않습니다! 그 소문은 누가 시작한 걸까요?
I did.
그랬어요.
I'm right! It was Jin Su. It is a truth that everyone knows–
내가 맞아요! 진수였습니다. 누구나 다 아는 사실이다.
That's right.
좋아요.
- Louis is awake. Louis, let's go. - It's a feast.
- 루이스가 깨어났어요. 루이스, 가자. - 잔치예요.
- It's smells good. - Get up. - Hi Wung.
- 냄새가 좋아요. - 일어나요. - 안녕하세요 웅.
But there's still some pajeon left.
하지만 아직 파전이 좀 남아있습니다.
- Ma'am, can you please wrap this up for me? - All right.
- 부인, 이것 좀 포장해 주시겠어요? - 괜찮은.
- Wrap it up please. - I'm full. Let's go.
- 마무리해주세요. - 배불러요. 갑시다.
Let's go.
갑시다.
Hey, bring this with you.
야, 이거 가지고 와라.
- Thank you. - Goodbye.
- 감사합니다. - 안녕히 가세요.
Defense successful.
방어에 성공했습니다.
It is so hard to grab a taxi today.
오늘은 택시 잡기가 너무 힘들어요.
It's chilly now that it's the evening.
이제 저녁이 되니까 쌀쌀하네요.
- The fourth attack is about to start. - Again?!
- 네 번째 공격이 시작됩니다. - 다시?!
Sae Yi's ulterior motive:
Sae Yi의 숨은 동기:
Physical contact
신체 접촉
It's cold, right?
춥죠?
- Is it that cold? - Yes.
- 그렇게 추워요? - 예.
Let's link arms, since it's cold.
추우니까 팔짱을 끼자.
Try this. You will be less cold.
이것을 시도해 보세요. 덜 추울 거예요.
Defense successful.
방어에 성공했습니다.
Don't stay up all night and go home. See you tomorrow.
밤새도록 깨어 있지 말고 집에 가십시오. 내일 봐요.
You are not going to the office?
사무실에 안 가시나요?
I'm tired. I want to go home. Good luck!
피곤해요. 나는 집에 가고 싶다. 행운을 빌어요!
Mission clear. Turning off bear mode.
미션 클리어. 곰 모드를 끄는 중입니다.
Everyone has a bulletin board in their hearts.
누구나 마음속에 게시판이 있습니다.
The same goes for Sae Yi.
세이이도 마찬가지다.
Become the best Art Director! Let's be a legend in the game world!
최고의 아트 디렉터가 되어보세요! 게임계의 전설이 되어보자!
I can do it! We are the eagle trio!
난 할 수 있어요! 우리는 독수리 트리오입니다!
I'm never going to get married!
나는 결코 결혼하지 않을 것입니다!
But if someday I get married ...
하지만 언젠가 결혼하게 된다면...
But if someday I do get married, it will probably be to Gu Wung.
하지만 언젠가 제가 결혼하게 된다면 아마 구웅과 결혼하게 될 것 같아요.
Episode 11 Naughty versus Naughtysaurus
Episode 11 Naughty 대 Naughtysaurus
It is 9 o'clock?
9시인가?
Crazy! Why did the alarm go off at 9 o'clock? What do I do?
미친! 알람은 왜 9시에 울렸나요? 어떻게 해야 하나요?
Yumi, today is Saturday.
유미 씨, 오늘은 토요일이에요.
Ah...That's right, today is Saturday.
아...맞아요 오늘은 토요일이에요.
Yumi, today is the day of your date with Wung.
유미 씨, 오늘은 웅 씨와 데이트하는 날이에요.
Yes, it is today.
네, 오늘이에요.
Sleeping again? Are you all sleeping?
또 자? 다들 자고 있나요?
Fashion, the date is at 12 p.m. We can sleep more.
패션, 날짜는 밤 12시. 우리는 더 잘 수 있습니다.
Are we not going to shop? I don't even remember the last time I did some shopping!
우리 쇼핑 안 갈 거야? 마지막으로 쇼핑을 한 게 언제인지 기억도 나지 않습니다!
Do you want to meet Wung in the same old clothes?
똑같은 낡은 옷을 입고 Wung을 만나고 싶나요?
Wung says Yumi looks cute no matter what she wears.
웅은 유미가 뭘 입든 귀여워 보인다고 말한다.
It might be cute the first couple of times, but for how long do you think that's going to work?
처음 몇 번은 귀여울 수도 있지만, 얼마나 오랫동안 그게 효과가 있을 거라고 생각하시나요?
Forget it.
잊어버리세요.
We need new clothes!
새 옷이 필요해요!
Yumi, wake up! We need to buy new clothes!
유미, 일어나! 우리는 새 옷을 사야 해!
God, I am earnestly praying. Please wake up Yumi!
하나님, 간절히 기도하고 있습니다. 유미를 깨워주세요!
Please allow Yumi to go shopping!
유미가 쇼핑할 수 있게 해주세요!
Your prayer has awakened me, Fashion.
당신의 기도가 나를 깨웠어요, 패션님.
God! You have come! Spending God!
하나님! 당신이 왔습니다! 지출의 신!
I will sing you a song because you are earnest.
당신이 진심이니까 노래를 불러드릴게요.
A song?
노래?
♪ Do Re Mi– Do Re Mi Fa— ♪
♪ 도레미– 도레미파— ♪
♪ Pa Pa Pa, words that ends in Pa— ♪
♪ Pa Pa Pa, Pa로 끝나는 단어— ♪
♪ Onions, spring onions, chives, and leeks, I want to buy these ♪ (all those end with "-pa" in Korean)
♪ 양파, 파, 부추, 부추 이거 사고 싶어요 ♪ (모두 "-pa"로 끝나는 한국어)
Wow!
우와!
Repeat the song with me.
나와 함께 노래를 반복해 보세요.
And Yumi will wake up.
그리고 유미는 깨어날 것이다.
♪ Pa Pa Pa, words that ends in Pa— ♪
♪ Pa Pa Pa, Pa로 끝나는 단어— ♪
♪ Onions, spring onions, chives, and leeks, I want to buy these ♪
♪ 양파, 파, 부추, 부추 이거 사고 싶어요 ♪
That's right! Is it...
좋아요! 그게...
Did the sale not end yet?
아직 세일 안끝났나요?
It looks so good on you.
정말 잘 어울리네요.
You found the perfect one right away.
당신은 바로 완벽한 것을 찾았습니다.
I had my eye on it from before. I will get this.
예전부터 눈여겨보고 있었는데 나는 이것을 얻을 것이다.
Of course. You can bring it out when you change.
물론. 갈아입을 때 꺼내시면 됩니다.
I'll just wear it out. Can you take the tag off?
그냥 입겠습니다. 태그 좀 떼어주실 수 있나요?
Will you do that? It's perfect for today's weather.
그렇게 하시겠습니까? 오늘 날씨에 딱이네요.
- One moment, please. - All right.
- 잠시만 기다려 주세요. - 괜찮은.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
These are the clothes you wore, here.
여기 당신이 입었던 옷이에요.
Do you know if there are any lockers nearby? I don't want to carry this around.
근처에 사물함이 있는지 아시나요? 나는 이것을 가지고 다니고 싶지 않습니다.
Should we hold onto it for you?
우리가 당신을 위해 그것을 붙잡아야 할까요?
Could you?
당신은 할 수 있습니까?
Yes, we can.
예, 가능합니다.
- Please write down your contact information here. - All right.
- 여기에 연락처를 적어주세요. - 괜찮은.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Gu Wung
구웅
Hello?
안녕하세요?
Of course, I'm up. I'm already out.
물론, 나는 일어났습니다. 나는 이미 나갔다.
Really? You stayed up all night?
정말? 밤새도록 계셨나요?
Then I'll go somewhere close to your apartment.
그럼 내가 네 아파트 근처로 갈게.
I'm near there right now.
나는 지금 거기 근처에 있습니다.
It's all right. I'll be drinking coffee.
괜찮아요. 나는 커피를 마실 것이다.
Yes.
예.
I'm heading down now. Where are you?
나는 지금 아래로 향하고 있다. 어디세요?
I'll go to you. It'll take me less than five minutes.
나는 당신에게 갈 것이다. 5분도 채 안 걸릴 것 같아요.
It's perfect. Glad you bought it, right?
완벽해요. 사서 다행이군요, 그렇죠?
Yumi, undo two buttons.
유미 씨, 버튼 두 개를 취소하세요.
So that your collarbone shows. That's your attractive point.
쇄골이 보이도록. 그게 당신의 매력이에요.
Who is that?
그 사람은 누구입니까?
Yumi's collarbone is sexy.
유미 쇄골이 섹시하네요
Naughty, you...!
버릇없어, 너...!
Let's undo them.
취소해 보겠습니다.
Yes. Just like that, Yumi.
예. 바로 그거야, 유미.
Don't give her useless advice. What do you know about fashion?
그녀에게 쓸데없는 조언을 하지 마세요. 패션에 대해 무엇을 알고 있나요?
You don't even wear pants!
너 바지도 안 입잖아!
Stop it!
그만해요!
Fashion isn't important. When are they going to kiss?
패션은 중요하지 않습니다. 그들은 언제 키스할 예정인가요?
- He said "kiss"! - How could he say that!
- 그가 "키스"라고 했어요! - 어떻게 그런 말을 할 수가 있지?
- I'm so excited! - Awesome!
- 정말 신난다! - 엄청난!
Naughty, what are you doing? Don't provoke the others!
장난 꾸러기, 뭐하는거야? 다른 사람을 자극하지 마십시오!
It's about time now.
이제 시간이 다가왔습니다.
We have to kiss today.
오늘은 키스해야 해.
Stop getting so excited! They've only met a couple of times.
너무 흥분하지 마세요! 그들은 단지 몇 번 만났을 뿐입니다.
A kiss isn't a coupon. We don't need to fill out stamps.
키스는 쿠폰이 아닙니다. 우리는 우표를 작성할 필요가 없습니다.
You just do it if you feel like it!
그냥 기분 좋으면 하세요!
- He's right. - That's true.
- 그 사람 말이 맞아요. - 사실이에요.
Who's right?
누가 맞나요?
- Yumi has waited long enough. I've waited long enough. - That's right. - He's right!
- 유미는 충분히 오래 기다렸어요. 나는 충분히 오래 기다렸다. - 좋아요. - 그 사람 말이 맞아요!
You can undo three buttons, Yumi! Undo them!
버튼 세 개를 취소할 수 있어요, 유미! 취소하세요!
No!
아니요!
It's not time for you to step in yet!
아직은 당신이 개입할 시간이 아닙니다!
Come here.
이리 오세요.
Undo other things too!
다른 것들도 취소하세요!
What just happened?
방금 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
Oh no! No wonder I was nervous that we might spill the coffee.
안 돼! 커피를 쏟을까봐 긴장한 것도 당연합니다.
This was so expensive!
이거 너무 비쌌어요!
What happened?
무슨 일이에요?
Did you fall?
넘어졌나요?
I spilled my coffee.
커피를 쏟았습니다.
You spilled a lot.
많이 쏟으셨네요.
So why would you call the Spending god? You're so dead!
그렇다면 왜 지출의 신이라고 부르겠습니까? 넌 정말 죽었어!
Calm down, Stingy!
진정해, 스팅기!
It'll be fine if we wash it right away.
바로 세탁하면 괜찮을 것 같아요.
She needs to change to continue their date.
데이트를 계속하려면 그녀는 옷을 갈아입어야 합니다.
There are the clothes she left behind at the store earlier.
그녀가 아까 가게에 놓고 간 옷들이 있어요.
You're right!
당신 말이 맞아요!
What should we do?
우리는 무엇을 해야 합니까?
It's all right. Actually, at the clothing store—
괜찮아요. 사실은 옷가게에서—
Let's go to my place.
내 집으로 가자.
What?
무엇?
He wants to go to his place? Let go of me!
그 사람이 자기 집으로 가고 싶어? 날 놔줘!
Naughty, stay still!
버릇없어, 가만히 있어!
If you come to my place and wash this immediately...
우리 집에 와서 바로 씻어주면...
Your place?
당신의 집은요?
Yes, my place.
응, 내 집이야.
Going to his place is a bit too much.
그 사람 집에 가는 건 좀 무리예요.
She can change at the clothing store and leave the dress at a dry cleaner.
옷가게에서 옷을 갈아입고 드레스는 세탁소에 맡길 수 있습니다.
It's a good thing we have another set of clothes.
옷 한 벌 더 있어서 다행이에요.
Let's go to his place!
그의 집으로 가자!
Let's go to Wung's place! It's an opportunity!
웅이 있는 곳으로 가자! 기회입니다!
What opportunity?
무슨 기회?
Kiss!
키스!
It's right there.
바로 거기 있어요.
But, at the clothing store...
그런데 옷가게에서는...
Yumi, let's go to Wung's place.
유미야, 웅이네 집으로 가자.
The clothing store?
옷가게?
- What?
- 무엇?
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
Come in.
들어오세요.
- Wait here. - All right.
- 여기서 기다려요. - 괜찮은.
It's clean.
깨끗해요.
How is it so clean?
어쩜 이렇게 깨끗해요?
Space Rabbit
우주 토끼
I don't have any size small clothes, but I think this is the smallest I own.
사이즈가 작은 옷은 없는데, 이게 제가 가진 것 중 가장 작은 것 같아요.
You should change so you can wash that dress right away.
그 옷을 바로 세탁할 수 있도록 갈아입어야 합니다.
Oh, yeah! This is where Wung showers!
아, 그래! 여기가 Wung이 샤워하는 곳이에요!
Would you like some coffee?
커피 좀 드시겠어요?
Yes! That sounds great!
예! 정말 좋은 것 같아요!
He must have showered recently. The scent is still lingering.
그 사람은 최근에 샤워를 했나 봐요. 아직도 향기가 남아있습니다.
The scent of sexy muskiness.
섹시한 머스키한 향.
I love it.
나는 그것을 좋아한다.
I like Wung because he's sexy.
나는 Wung이 섹시하기 때문에 좋아해요.
Yumi, what are you thinking about?
유미 씨, 무슨 생각해요?
%#*&^#%!
%#*&^#%!
Somebody drag him away before Yumi gets weird!
유미가 이상해지기 전에 누군가 그를 끌고 가세요!
Let go of me!
날 놔줘!
- Sorry, guys! - The tree, @!#$, the tree!
- 미안해요! - 나무, @!#$, 나무!
You @*$^^$%^#!
당신은 @*$^^$%^#!
Guys, Wung wasn't thinking of this.
여러분, Wung은 이것을 생각하지 않았습니다.
He invited her over with innocent intentions, so let's not get excited!
순수한 의도로 그녀를 초대했으니 너무 흥분하지 말자!
Yes, let's not get excited.
응, 흥분하지 말자.
The clothes are too big, right?
옷이 너무 크죠?
Yes, a bit.
네, 조금요.
That was the smallest size I had.
제가 가지고 있는 사이즈 중 가장 작은 사이즈였어요.
No! No!
아니요! 아니요!
Naughtysaurus, calm down.
너티사우루스님, 진정하세요.
Calm down.
진정하다.
Yumi is wearing my clothes!
유미가 내 옷을 입고 있어요!
Her collarbones are so sexy.
쇄골이 너무 섹시해요.
Everyone grab him!
모두 그를 잡아라!
- Come together. - All right. All right.
- 같이 오세요. - 괜찮은. 괜찮은.
Grab him! Grab him!
그를 잡아! 그를 잡아!
It is very big.
그것은 매우 크다.
It is.
그것은.
But that's the smallest that I have.
하지만 그것은 내가 가진 것 중 가장 작은 것입니다.
But you're still cute.
하지만 당신은 여전히 ​​귀엽습니다.
Am I cute again? I guess I am the embodiment of cuteness.
나 또 귀엽지? 저는 귀여움의 화신인 것 같아요.
Give it to me.
나에게 주세요.
Calm down. Calm down. Calm down.
진정하다. 진정하다. 진정하다.
You should act like a gentleman, okay?
신사처럼 행동해야 해, 알았지?
You did well till now. Good job.
지금까지 잘 지내셨어요. 잘했어요.
You can't mess up here.
여기서 엉망이 될 수는 없습니다.
Yumi will be disgusted to find you–
유미가 널 보면 역겨워할 거야–
Calm down, okay?
진정해, 알았지?
Isn't that fabric softener?
섬유유연제 아닌가요?
What?
무엇?
That's fabric softener!
섬유유연제에요!
They're going to kiss! Kiss!
그들은 키스할 거예요! 키스!
Stay still!
가만히 있어라!
Danger detected! Danger detected!
위험이 감지되었습니다! 위험이 감지되었습니다!
Entering into the carbon dioxide zone.
이산화탄소 구역으로 들어갑니다.
It's an area where you can feel the carbon dioxide emitted from each other.
서로서로 배출되는 이산화탄소를 느낄 수 있는 공간이다.
If you enter this area, Naughtysaurus will get out of control.
이 지역에 들어가면 Naughtysaurus가 통제 불능 상태가 됩니다.
Step back, Wung!
물러서라, 웅!
I said step back!
물러서라고 했어요!
You're getting ...
점점...
What?
무엇?
You're getting a call.
전화가 옵니다.
I'll do this.
내가 할게.
Leaving the carbon dioxide zone.
이산화탄소 구역을 떠납니다.
Hello?
안녕하세요?
Yes, I'm home, why?
응, 나 집에 왔는데, 왜?
I think you have to come here. The file isn't opening all of the sudden.
내 생각엔 당신이 여기로 와야 할 것 같아요. 파일이 갑자기 열리지 않습니다.
What?
무엇?
Something must have gone wrong while updating the Unity version. Louis can't open it either.
Unity 버전을 업데이트하는 동안 문제가 발생한 것 같습니다. 루이스도 열 수 없습니다.
Ask him to come quickly. No, let me talk to him.
그에게 빨리 오라고 하세요. 아니, 그 사람이랑 얘기 좀 하자.
Hello. Wung, there's a problem.
안녕하세요. 웅, 문제가 생겼어요.
Come quickly.
빨리 오세요.
Okay.
좋아요.
Did something happen?
무슨 일이 있었나요?
Unfortunately, I think I have to go to my office.
안타깝게도 사무실에 가야 할 것 같아요.
- Right now? - Yes.
- 지금 바로? - 예.
There seems to be a problem. It's a bit urgent.
문제가 있는 것 같습니다. 좀 급해요.
I just started the washing machine.
방금 세탁기를 시작했어요.
Do you want to stay here? I'll be right back.
여기에 머물고 싶나요? 곧 돌아올게요.
When will you come back?
언제 돌아올 거예요?
I'm not sure.
잘 모르겠습니다.
I don't think it will be over soon.
곧 끝나지 않을 것 같아요.
Being here alone is ...
여기에 혼자 있는 건...
- Is that a bit too much? - Yes.
- 좀 너무한가? - 예.
A bit.
조금.
But you can't go out dressed like this anyway.
하지만 어차피 이런 옷을 입고 나갈 수는 없어요.
You need something to change into.
변화할 무언가가 필요합니다.
I do have something to wear.
입을 게 좀 있어요.
- Excuse me. - Welcome.
- 실례합니다. - 환영.
Do you have the clothes that a woman left here this morning?
오늘 아침에 여자가 여기 두고 간 옷이 있나요?
Yes.
예.
- Her name is... - Kim Yumi.
- 그 사람 이름은... - 김유미.
Yes. Here it is.
예. 여기 있습니다.
- Thank you. - No problem.
- 감사합니다. - 괜찮아요.
The taxi is here.
택시가 여기 있어요.
Go ahead.
계속하세요.
Let's ride together. I'll drop you home and then go.
함께 타자. 집에 데려다 주고 가겠습니다.
There's no need. You're already late.
필요하지 않습니다. 당신은 이미 늦었어요.
Go quickly. I can just take the bus.
빨리 가세요. 그냥 버스를 타면 돼요.
Go quickly.
빨리 가세요.
I-I'll call you.
나-전화할게.
♫ We know ♫
♫ 우리는 알고 있어요 ♫
Today's date is over, Naughty.
오늘 데이트는 끝났어, 너티.
Get some sleep now.
이제 좀 자세요.
They could have kissed.
그들은 키스했을 수도 있습니다.
He's calmed down now.
그는 이제 진정되었습니다.
The house is too dangerous. He almost went out of control!
집이 너무 위험해요. 그는 거의 통제 불능 상태가 되었습니다!
Let's not bring her home again.
그녀를 다시는 집에 데려오지 말자.
♫ I feel I am changing ♫
♫ 내가 변하고 있는 것 같아요 ♫
♫  For us, now even the small things ♫
♫ 우리에게는 이제 작은 것까지도 ♫
It worked!
효과가 있었어요!
Did it?
그랬나요?
I think so.
그렇게 생각해요.
It's done!
끝났어요!
Good job, Wung!
잘했어요, 웡!
Wung, if it weren't for you ... Seriously, we almost lost everything!
Wung, 당신이 아니었다면 ... 정말, 우리는 거의 모든 것을 잃을 뻔했습니다!
What time is it?
지금은 몇시입니까?
You must be hungry. Let's go out! Let's eat something really good today, okay?
배가 고프겠군요. 나가자! 오늘은 정말 맛있는 거 먹자, 응?
I have to go, you two just eat together!
나 가야 해, 둘이서 밥만 먹어!
Why? Aren't you hungry?
왜? 배고프지 않나요?
- I'm not hungry. - He came here in the middle of a date.
- 배고프지 않아요. - 데이트 도중에 오셨어요.
- Go ahead, CEO. - I'll get going.
- 어서 가세요, CEO님. - 갈게요.
- See you on Monday. - Good job.
- 월요일에 봐요. - 잘했어요.
What did I do wrong? Yes, it's all been revealed anyway.
내가 뭘 잘못했나요? 네 어쨌든 다 밝혀졌습니다.
Yes, I'm going to say something to Comedy Big League*. (Korean comedy show)
네, 코미디 빅 리그*에 한 말씀 드리겠습니다. (한국 코미디 쇼)
Jang Do Yeon, this dance.
장도연, 이 춤.
- This will be broadcasted, right? - Yes.
- 이거 방송되는 거 맞죠? - 예.
But why isn't what I did broadcasted?
그런데 왜 내가 한 일이 방송되지 않는 걸까요?
Why can't it?
왜 그럴 수 없습니까?
Gu Wung
구웅
Hello?
안녕하세요?
Yes, I'm home. Are you done?
네, 집에 왔어요. 끝났나요?
I just finished and came home now. I'll bring you your dress.
방금 마치고 집에 왔습니다. 네 드레스를 가져다줄게.
Oh, no, it's fine. Give it to me next time.
아뇨, 괜찮아요. 다음에는 나에게 주세요.
I'll stop by now.
지금 들를게요.
Give it to me next time we see each other. You must be tired now.
다음에 우리 만날 때 나한테 주세요. 지금 피곤하시겠군요.
But I would like to stop by now.
하지만 지금은 잠시 들러보고 싶습니다.
Can't I come to see you now?
지금 보러 가면 안 돼요?
All right. Come by.
괜찮은. 오세요.
I'll contact you when I arrive.
도착하면 연락드릴게요.
There's something weird about Yumi's behavior.
유미의 행동에는 뭔가 이상한 점이 있습니다.
She left her clothes at the clothing store.
그녀는 옷가게에 옷을 두고 내렸습니다.
That clothing store is only a 3-minute walk away from where the coffee was spilled.
그 옷가게는 커피를 쏟은 곳에서 도보로 3분 거리에 있다.
It was closer than Wung's house which is a 5-minute walk away.
걸어서 5분 거리인 웅씨 집보다 더 가까웠다.
Yet, she came to our home and changed into Wung's clothes.
그런데 그 분이 우리 집에 오셔서 웅의 옷으로 갈아입으셨어요.
Why?
왜?
I'm in front of your house.
나 지금 네 집 앞에 있어.
Why are you so late?
왜 이렇게 늦었어?
I wanted to iron it before coming.
오기 전에 다림질하고 싶었어요.
You didn't have to iron it.
다림질을 할 필요가 없었습니다.
Have you had dinner?
저녁 먹었어?
No, not yet.
아니요, 아직은 아닙니다.
Oh, really? Let's go eat then. I'll pay!
오, 진짜? 그럼 먹으러 가자. 내가 지불할게!
But...
하지만...
why did you come to my place when you had clothes?
옷이 있는데 왜 우리 집에 왔나요?
Sorry?
죄송합니다?
The clothing store was closer than my place.
옷가게가 우리 집보다 더 가까웠어요.
I ...
나는 ...
didn't think of that.
그건 생각하지 못했습니다.
You didn't think of that?
그런 생각은 안 해보셨나요?
That's right, because I was flustered.
그렇구나, 당황했으니까.
I remembered later that I had bought clothes.
나중에 생각나서 옷을 샀어요.
Oh, really?
오, 진짜?
Then what else could it be?
그렇다면 또 무엇이 있을까요?
I don't know what it could be, that's why I'm asking.
그게 뭔지 모르겠어서 물어보는 거에요.
I told you I didn't think of that.
나는 그런 생각을 하지 않았다고 말했다.
All right.
괜찮은.
Why are you laughing?
왜 웃어요?
Because you're cute.
왜냐면 당신은 귀엽거든요.
You're ridiculous. You always say I'm cute.
당신은 말도 안돼. 당신은 항상 내가 귀엽다고 말해요.
What do you feel like eating? This area is famous for ...
먹으면서 어떤 느낌이 드나요? 이 지역은 ...
kimchijjim* ... (*braised kimchi)
김치찜* ... (*김치찜)
♫ When I'm wandering on the street after a tiring day ♫
♫ 지친 하루를 마치고 거리를 헤매고 있을 때 ♫
♫ When I look up at the sky full of stars ♫
♫ 별이 가득한 하늘을 올려다볼 때 ♫
♫ Even if I don't extend my hand the feeling of warmth ♫
♫ 손을 뻗지 않아도 따뜻한 느낌 ♫
♫ comes and comforts me ♫
♫ 와서 나를 위로해 주어요 ♫
♫ Like a star ♫
♫ 별처럼 ♫
♫ Always be at my side ♫
♫ 항상 내 옆에 있어줘 ♫
♫ Like a star shining in the dark night ♫
♫ 어두운 밤에 빛나는 별처럼 ♫
♫ Always shine brightly by my side ♫
♫ 언제나 내 곁에서 밝게 빛나줘 ♫
♫ Like a star ♫
♫ 별처럼 ♫
♫ while looking at me smile brightly ♫
♫ 나를 바라보며 밝게 웃어 ♫
♫ You who are so precious to me ♫
♫ 나에게 너무나 소중한 당신 ♫
♫ Always by my side, remain at my side ♫
♫ 언제나 내 곁에 있어줘, 내 곁에 있어 ♫
♫ One step closer, come just a little closer ♫
♫ 한 걸음 더 가까이, 조금만 더 가까이 와 ♫
♫ Hug me so I won't be lonely ♫
♫ 외롭지 않게 안아주세요 ♫
♫ I won't change as time passes. ♫
♫ 시간이 지나도 나는 변하지 않을 거예요. ♫
♫ Like a star ♫
♫ 별처럼 ♫
♫ Always be at my side ♫
♫ 항상 내 옆에 있어줘 ♫
♫ Like a star shining in the dark night ♫
♫ 어두운 밤에 빛나는 별처럼 ♫
♫ Always shine brightly by my side ♫
♫ 언제나 내 곁에서 밝게 빛나줘 ♫
Yumi's Cells
유미의 세포
Preview There's something I really want to do with you.
미리보기 내가 당신과 꼭 하고 싶은 일이 있어요.
I don't know whether you will like it or not.
당신이 그것을 좋아할지 아닐지 모르겠습니다.
- Then let's go to my place. - What?
- 그럼 우리 집으로 가자. - 무엇?
Naughty, don't get too ahead of yourself.
장난 꾸러기, 너무 앞서 나가지 마십시오.
This is really good. Who made this?
정말 좋습니다. 누가 만들었나요?
A man and a woman can't be just friends!
남자와 여자는 단지 친구가 될 수 없다!
Because ... they just can't!
왜냐면...그들은 그럴 수 없거든요!
Is this Sae Yi? She is pretty.
이 세이인가요? 그녀는 예쁘다.
I have to stop by the office, do you want to go with me after eating this?
나 사무실에 들러야 하는데, 이거 먹고 같이 갈래?
But how do you know my name?
그런데 내 이름을 어떻게 아세요?